{
    "subject": "Anne_of_Kiev",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Henry_I_of_France",
    "human_readable": "Anne of Kiev is married to Henry I of France.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9756802320480347,
            "question": "Was Henry I of France married to someone from Kiev?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9262464046478271,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Anne of Kiev and Henry I of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8790731430053711,
            "question": "Who is Anne of Kiev married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.873712420463562,
            "question": "Who was Henry I of France married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.821229875087738,
            "question": "Name the wife of Henry I of France."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6240334510803223,
            "question": "What was the significance of Anne of Kiev's marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6125967502593994,
            "question": "To whom did Anne of Kiev belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5025116801261902,
            "question": "What was the name of Henry I's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4000178575515747,
            "question": "What role did Anne of Kiev play in French history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38182780146598816,
            "question": "Was Anne of Kiev related to a king?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Anne of Kiev is married to Henry I of France.",
            "html": "yago_28389_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Anne of Kiev play in French history?",
            "html": "yago_28389_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Henry I's wife?",
            "html": "yago_28389_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Anne of Kiev belong?",
            "html": "yago_28389_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28389_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Anne of Kiev was married to King Henry I of France. Therefore, the triple \"Anne of Kiev is married to Henry I of France\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}